PRAVEEN KUMAR

% 7827598996

☐ link2pk@gmail.com Bē be.net/link2pk (Portfolio)

Creative graphics designer having an eye for typography, visual aspects to build user interfaces and layouts for web, print, and hybrid applications that provide great user experience using Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma, InDesign, Corel Draw and others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer, ValueCoders Services LLP (A Vinove Company), Dec 2021 - Present Senior Software Engineer, Appster LLP, Oct 2017 - Dec 2018 Software Engineer, Appster LLP, Apr 2016 - Oct 2017 Web Developer, Appster LLP, Dec 2014 - Mar 2016 Designer, Convergent Technologies, Mar 2014 - Dec 2014 Web Designer, Sagacious Softwares(now Digital HIVE), Mar 2014 - Dec 2014 Ul Designer, Webreinvent Technologies Pvt Ltd, Aug 2012 - Jul 2013

My role was to create UI elements, web design, branding, flyers, banners, and background images for special events and holidays, etc.

During my work, I got the opportunity to work with top clients like Samsung, Apple, Eicher, NIIT, and other small and medium sized businesses.

Please have a look at my design work on Behance.

EDUCATION

MSc in Information Technology, De Montfort University, Leicester, United Kingdom, 2011 BE in Electronics and Communications, Institute of Technology & Management, Gurgaon (now NorthCap University), 2008